Capra Press mss., 1955-2010 LMC 2228
Lilly Library
- II. Capra Press publications
  - Kicknosway, Faye
    - A Man is a Hook, MS, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 31-32)
    - A Man is a Hook, Page proofs, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - You Can Walk on the Sky, Artwork and proofs, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - You Can Walk on the Sky, MS, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Kirsch, Robert
    - Lives Works and Transformations, Cover art, 1978 (Box 58, Folder Unknown)
    - Lives Works and Transformations, Miscellaneous, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Lives Works and Transformations, MS, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Lives Works and Transformations, Proofs, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 18-19)
  - Knoll, Zig
    - Not My Mother's Child, Galleys, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Not My Mother's Child, MS, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Koehler, Ann
    - A Shaggy Dog's Book of Hours, Correspondence, 1991 (Box 50, Folder 17)
    - A Shaggy Dog's Book of Hours, Photographs, 1991 (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - Krieger, David
    - Waging Peace in the Nuclear Age, Correspondence, 1988 (Box 45, Folder 15)
    - Waging Peace in the Nuclear Age, MS, 1988 (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - Krysl, Marilyn
    - Honey, Artwork, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 27)
    - Honey, Final publication, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 28)
    - Honey, MS, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 24-25)
    - Honey, Proofs, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - Lachtman, Howard
    - Sherlock Slept Here, Afterward, 1985 (Box 39, Folder 25)
    - Sherlock Slept Here, Book production materials, 1985 (Box 39, Folder 26)
    - Sherlock Slept Here, Chapter revisions, 1985 (Box 39, Folder 27)
    - Sherlock Slept Here, Computer paper MS printout, 1985 (Box 39, Folder 28-29)
    - Sherlock Slept Here, Correspondence, 1985 (Box 39, Folder 30)
    - Sherlock Slept Here, Page proofs, 1985 (Box 40, Folder 1-2)
    - Sherlock Slept Here, Revised MS, 1985 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Sherlock Slept Here, Unbound dummy, 1985 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Sherlock Slept Here, Uncorrected proofs, 1985 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Sherlock Slept Here, Xerox proofs, 1985 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Lanchester, Elsa
    - A Gamut of Girls, Correspondence and artwork, 1987 (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - A Gamut of Girls, MS, 1987 (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - A Gamut of Girls, Uncorrected proofs, 1987 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Le Guin, Ursula K.
    - Buffalo Gals and Other Animal Presences, Art, 1987 (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - Buffalo Gals and Other Animal Presences, Correspondence, 1987 (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - Buffalo Gals and Other Animal Presences, MS, 1987 (Box 43, Folder 12)
    - Buffalo Gals and Other Animal Presences, Proofs, 1987 (Box 43, Folder 13)
    - The Visionary and Wonders Hidden, MS, 1984 (Box 36, Folder 25-26)
    - The Visionary and Wonders Hidden, Proofs, 1984 (Box 36, Folder 27-29)
    - The Visionary, Artwork, 1984 (Box 36, Folder 23)
    - The Visionary, Correspondence, 1984 (Box 36, Folder 24)
    - Wild Angels, MS and artwork, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Wild Angels, Proofs, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Lee, Hector
    - Heroes Villains and Ghosts, Correspondence, 1984 (Box 36, Folder 30)
    - Heroes Villains and Ghosts, Dummy, 1984 (Box 36, Folder 31)
    - Heroes Villains and Ghosts, MS, 1984 (Box 36, Folder 32)
    - The Bodega War, Corrected pages, 1987 (Box 43, Folder 14)
    - The Bodega War, Correspondence and art, 1987 (Box 43, Folder 15)
    - The Bodega War, MS printout, 1987 (Box 43, Folder 16)
    - The Bodega War, Original MS, 1987 (Box 43, Folder 17)
    - The Bodega War, Proofs, 1987 (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - Leen, Daniel
    - Copy of 1978 issue, 1979 (Box 27, Folder 30)
    - Miscellaneous, 1979 (Box 27, Folder 31)
    - The Freighthopper's Manual for North America, Edited copy for reprinting, 1979 (Box 27, Folder 29)
    - The Freighthopper's Manual for North America, Paste-ups from first printing, 1979 (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - Leigh, Carol
    - California Gardens, Correspondence, 1992 (Box 51, Folder 14)
    - California Gardens, First proof, 1992 (Box 51, Folder 15)
    - California Gardens, Original MS, 1992 (Box 51, Folder 16)
    - California Gardens, Proofs and indexing materials, 1992 (Box 51, Folder 17)
    - California Gardens, Rough drafts, 1992 (Box 51, Folder 18)
  - Lentz, Joan
    - Birdwatching, Artwork, 1985 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Birdwatching, Boards, 1985 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Birdwatching, Galleys, 1985 (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Birdwatching, MS, 1985 (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - Birdwatching, Page proofs, 1985 (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - Birdwatching, Printer's MS, 1985 (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - Birdwatching, Proofs and galleys, 1985 (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - Great Birding Trips, Correspondence and illustrations, 1987 (Box 43, Folder 19)
    - Great Birding Trips, MS, 1987 (Box 43, Folder 20-21)
    - Great Birding Trips, Proofs, 1987 (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - Levenson, Roger
    - Women in Printing, Proofs, 1994 (Box 55, Folder 11-12)
  - Liddy, James
    - Baudelaire's Bar Flowers, MS and artwork, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Baudelaire's Bar Flowers, Proofs, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Lifshin, Lyn
    - Lips Unsealed, Correspondence, 1989 (Box 48, Folder 3-4)
    - Old House Poems, MS & artwork, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Old House Poems, Proofs, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Loam, Jayson
    - Hot Springs, edited MS, 1979 (Box 27, Folder 34)
    - Hot Springs, Misc., 1979 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Hot Springs, MS, 1979 (Box 27, Folder 32-33)
  - Lollar, Amanda
    - The Bat in my Pocket, Proofs, 1992 (Box 51, Folder 19)
  - London, Jack
    - Young Wolf, Correspondence, 1984 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Young Wolf, Galleys, 1984 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Young Wolf, MS, 1984 (Box 37, Folder 3-5)
    - Young Wolf, Photos, 1984 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Young Wolf, Proofs, 1984 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Long, Sam
    - Scissors Sam, Artwork, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Scissors Sam, MS, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Scissors Sam, Proofs, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 18-19)
  - Loomis, Edward
    - Bank Burning, Galleys and artwork, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Bank Burning, MS, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - MacDonald, Ross
    - Self Portrait, Correspondence, 1981 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Self Portrait, Cover and book design, 1981 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Self Portrait, MS, 1981 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Self Portrait, MS and drafts, 1981 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Self Portrait, Promotional and publication materials, 1981 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Self Portrait, Proofs, 1981 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Marcus, Morton
    - The Santa Cruz Mountain Poems, MS, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 23-25)
    - Where the Oceans Cover Us, Artwork, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Where the Oceans Cover Us, MS, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Where the Oceans Cover Us, Proofs, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Martin, Jay
    - Always Merry and Bright, Corrected proofs, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Always Merry and Bright, Galleys, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 9-10)
    - Always Merry and Bright, Index, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Always Merry and Bright, Miscellaneous, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Always Merry and Bright, MS, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 2-6)
    - Always Merry and Bright, Revised MS, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Matheson, Richard
    - The Path, Correspondence, 1993 (Box 52, Folder 11)
    - The Path, Edited proofs, 1993 (Box 52, Folder 12)
    - The Path, Proofs, 1993 (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - McAllister, Callista
    - Pornella, MS and proofs, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - McCurdy, Michael
    - McCurdy's World, A Postcard Book, Book design materials, 1991 (Box 50, Folder 19)
  - McFaddan, Elizabeth
    - Out of the Past, MS, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - McKinney, John
    - California Coastal Trails, MS, 1983 (Box 34, Folder 10-11)
    - California Coastal Trails, Printing costs and miscellaneous, 1983 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - California Coastal Trails, Proofs, 1983 (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - The Day Hiker's Guide, Book design, 1981 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - The Day Hiker's Guide, Correspondence, 1981 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - The Day Hiker's Guide, MS, 1981 (Box 31, Folder 9-10)
    - The Day Hiker's Guide, Proofs, 1981 (Box 31, Folder 11-12)
  - McNutt, Joni
    - In Praise of Wine, Correction pages, 1993 (Box 52, Folder 14)
    - In Praise of Wine, Correspondence, 1993 (Box 52, Folder 15)
    - In Praise of Wine, Dummies, 1993 (Box 52, Folder 16)
    - In Praise of Wine, Final proof, 1993 (Box 52, Folder 17)
    - In Praise of Wine, Marked copies, 1993 (Box 52, Folder 18)
    - In Praise of Wine, MS, 1993 (Box 52, Folder 19-20)
    - In Praise of Wine, Proofs, 1993 (Box 52, Folder 21-22)
  - McQuarrie, Jack
    - Wildcrafting, Artwork, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Wildcrafting, Dummy, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Wildcrafting, Dummy and photos, 1975 (Box 59, Folder Unknown)
    - Wildcrafting, MS, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 14-15)
    - Wildcrafting, Proofs, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Wildcrafting, Royalty statements, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Meltzer, David
    - Bark, Galleys, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Bark, MS, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Mendoza, Tony
    - Ernie's Postcard Book, Author's dummy, 1985 (Box 40, Folder 14)
    - Ernie's Postcard Book, Book production material, 1985 (Box 40, Folder 15)
    - Ernie's Postcard Book, Correspondence, 1985 (Box 40, Folder 16)
    - Ernie's Postcard Book, Correspondence, 1989 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Ernie's Postcard Book, Miscellaneous, 1985 (Box 40, Folder 17)
    - Ernie's Postcard Book, Mock-up, 1985 (Box 40, Folder 18-19)
    - Ernie's Postcard Book, MS, 1985 (Box 40, Folder 20)
    - Ernie's Postcard Book, Photos and page proofs, 1989 (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Ernie's Postcard Book, Proofs, 1985 (Box 40, Folder 21)
  - Metz, Jerred
    - Temperate Voluptuary, Artwork, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Temperate Voluptuary, MS, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Temperate Voluptuary, Proofs and art, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Meyer, Justin
    - Plain Talk about Fine Wine, Correspondence, 1987 (Box 43, Folder 23)
    - Plain Talk about Fine Wine, Cover designs, 1987 (Box 43, Folder 24)
    - Plain Talk About Fine Wine, Illustrations, 1987 (Box 58, Folder Unknown)
    - Plain Talk About Fine Wine, MS, 1987 (Box 58, Folder Unknown)
    - Plain Talk about Fine Wine, Proofs, 1987 (Box 43, Folder 25)
  - Millar, Kenneth
    - On Crime Writing, Galleys, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - On Crime Writing, MS, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Miller, Henry
    - Book of Friends, Book design material, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Book of Friends, Final corrections, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Book of Friends, Final proofs, 1987 (Box 43, Folder 26)
    - Book of Friends, Jacket blurb, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Book of Friends, MS, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 19-20)
    - Book of Friends, Page proofs, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Book of Friends, Proofs, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 12-18)
    - Book of Friends, Request for review copies, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Book of Friends, Revision copy, 1987 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Book of Friends, Vol. 1 printout, 1987 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Book of Friends, Vol. 2 printout, 1987 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Book of Friends, Vol. 3 printout, 1987 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - First Impressions of Greece, Artwork, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - First Impressions of Greece, Contracts, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - First Impressions of Greece, MS, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - First Impressions of Greece, Proofs and galleys, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Four Visions of America, Corrected MS, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Four Visions of America, Cover design materials, 1977 (Box 60, Folder Unknown)
    - Four Visions of America, Galleys, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Four Visions of America, MS, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Four Visions of America, Page proofs, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Four Visions of America, Paste-ups, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Henry Miller's Hamlet Letters, Correspondence, 1987 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Henry Miller's Hamlet Letters, MS, 1987 (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Henry Miller's Hamlet Letters, Page proofs, 1987 (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - Henry Miller's Hamlet Letters, Printout, 1987 (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - Joey, Corrected galleys, 1979 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Joey, Cover art, 1979 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Joey, Galleys, 1979 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Joey, Misc., 1979 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Joey, MS, 1979 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Joey, Page proofs, 1979 (Box 28, Folder 5-6)
    - Mother China, Proofs, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - My Bike and other Friends, Book design materials, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - My Bike and other Friends, MS, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - My Bike and other Friends, Page proofs, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 15-16)
    - My Bike and other Friends, Paste-ups, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - On Turning Eighty, MS and proofs, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Reflections on Death, MS, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Reflections, Book design materials, 1981 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Reflections, Correspondence, 1981 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Reflections, Drafts, 1981 (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Reflections, MS, 1981 (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - Reflections, Proofs, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Reflections, Proofs, 1981 (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - Sextet, Copy for stripper, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Sextet, Galleys, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Sextet, Paste-ups, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - The Waters Reglitterized, Edited proofs, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - The Waters Reglitterized, Galleys, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - The Waters Reglitterized, Proofs, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - The World of Lawrence, MS, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 29-32)
    - True Bear Stories, Correspondence, 1987 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Millman, Lawrence
    - A Kayak Full of Ghosts, Correspondence, 1987 (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - A Kayak Full of Ghosts, MS, 1987 (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - A Kayak Full of Ghosts, Proofs, 1987 (Box 44, Folder 12-13)
    - Wolverine Creates the World, Correspondence, 1993 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Wolverine Creates the World, Edited proofs, 1993 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Wolverine Creates the World, Proofs, 1993 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Millman, Mary
    - Master of Line, MS, 1994 (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - Mingo, Jack
    - The Official Couch…, Author's MS, 1983 (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - The Official Couch…, Correspondence, 1983 (Box 34, Folder 15-16)
    - The Official Couch…, Discards, 1983 (Box 34, Folder 17)
    - The Official Couch…, Miscellaneous, 1983 (Box 34, Folder 18)
    - The Official Couch…, Proofs, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Morgan, Richard
    - Patchen's Lost Plays, Art and photos, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Patchen's Lost Plays, Book design materials, 1977 (Box 60, Folder Unknown)
    - Patchen's Lost Plays, Clippings, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Patchen's Lost Plays, Galley proofs, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Patchen's Lost Plays, MS, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Patchen's Lost Plays, Paste-ups, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Patchen's Lost Plays, Royalties, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Morse, Peter
    - Popular Art, Artwork and photos, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - Popular Art, Galleys, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - Popular Art, MS, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Popular Art, Page proofs and paste-ups, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Mullan, Arthur
    - Spy, Edited printout, 1987 (Box 44, Folder 14-15)
    - Spy, Proofs, 1987 (Box 44, Folder 16-17)
  - Mustapha
    - Schoolin' Home Style, Dummy, 1975 (Box 59, Folder Unknown)
    - Schoolin' Homestyle, Art and photos, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Schoolin' Homestyle, Contracts, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - Schoolin' Homestyle, Dummy, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - Schoolin' Homestyle, Misc., 1975 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - Schoolin' Homestyle, Proofs, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Schoolin' Homestyle, Sign, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Nabokov, Peter
    - Indian Running, Contracts and permissions, 1981 (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - Indian Running, Correspondence, 1981 (Box 31, Folder 19)
    - Indian Running, Cover design, 1981 (Box 31, Folder 20)
    - Indian Running, MS, 1981 (Box 31, Folder 21)
    - Indian Running, Original MS, 1981 (Box 31, Folder 22)
    - Indian Running, Promo and publicity, 1981 (Box 31, Folder 23)
    - Indian Running, Proofs, 1981 (Box 31, Folder 24)
  - Nathan, Robert
    - Evening Song, Cover design and page proofs, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Evening Song, Galleys and proofs, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Neff, Wallace Jr.
    - Architect of California's Golden Age, Correspondence, 1987 (Box 44, Folder 18-21)
    - Architect of California's Golden Age, Edited MS, 1987 (Box 44, Folder 22)
  - Neumeyer, Peter
    - Why We Have Day and Night, Correspondence, 1982 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Neutra, Richard
    - Nature Near, Book design materials, 1989 (Box 48, Folder 7-8)
    - Nature Near, Correspondence, 1989 (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - Nature Near, MS, 1989 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Newcomer, Rebecca
    - A Mother's Journal for her Son, Correspondence, 1988 (Box 45, Folder 17)
    - A Mother's Journal for her Son, MS, 1988 (Box 45, Folder 18)
    - A Mother's Journal for her Son, Proofs, 1988 (Box 45, Folder 19-20)
  - Nietzke, Ann
    - Windowlight, Correspondence, 1981 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Windowlight, MS, 1981 (Box 32, Folder 4-6)
    - Windowlight, Printing costs, 1981 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Windowlight, Proofs, 1981 (Box 32, Folder 2-3)
    - Windowlight, Xerox of final MS, 1981 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Nin, Anais
    - Back-to-Back #2, Correspondence, 1984 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Back-to-Back #2, Galleys, 1984 (Box 37, Folder 9-10)
    - Back-to-Back #2, Nin material, 1984 (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - Back-to-Back #2, Nin MS, 1984 (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - Back-to-Back #2, Okamoto MS, 1984 (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - Back-to-Back #2, Page proofs, 1984 (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - Paris Revisited, Galleys, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Paris Revisited, MS, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - No author
    - Bibliographical checklist, Galleys, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Bibliographical checklist, MS, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Nolan, William
    - Hemingway, MS, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Hemingway, Photographs, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - The Books of Max Brand, Proofs, 1984 (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - O'Byrne, Nan
    - Hokusai, Summary, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Paulsen, Dennis
    - Voices of Survival in the Nuclear Age, corrections, 1986 (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - Voices of Survival in the Nuclear Age, correspondence and draft materials, 1986 (Box 42, Folder 12-13)
    - Voices of Survival in the Nuclear Age, front and back matter, 1986 (Box 42, Folder 14)
    - Voices of Survival in the Nuclear Age, MS, 1986 (Box 42, Folder 15-16)
    - Voices of Survival in the Nuclear Age, proofs, 1986 (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - Peake, Katy
    - A Four Gathering, MS, 1981 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - A Four Gathering, Paste-ups, 1981 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - A Four Gathering, Proofs, 1981 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - A Four Gathering, Unsewn copy, 1981 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Perera, Padma
    - Dr. Salaam, Galleys, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Dr. Salaam, MS, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Perera, Victor
    - Loch Ness, Engraver's proofs, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Loch Ness, MS, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Perry, Paul
    - Chinese Fitness, correspondence, 1981 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Chinese Fitness, first draft, 1981 (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Chinese Fitness, ms, 1981 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Peters, Fritz
    - Boyhood with Gurdjieff, Book design material, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 36)
    - Boyhood with Gurdjieff, Correspondence, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 34)
    - Boyhood with Gurdjieff, Photocopy of original 1960 printing, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 33)
    - Boyhood with Gurdjieff, Preface by Henry Miller, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 35)
  - Peterson, David
    - Racks, correspondence & proofs, 1990 (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Racks, proof, 1990 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Powell, Lawrence Clark
    - The Evening Redness, Correspondence and MS, 1988 (Box 45, Folder 21)
    - The Evening Redness, Preface and artwork, 1988 (Box 45, Folder 22)
    - The Evening Redness, Proofs, 1988 (Box 45, Folder 23)
    - An Orange Grove Boyhood, Printout, 1988 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - An Orange Grove Boyhood, Proofs, 1988 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Angels Burning, Galleys, 1987 (Box 44, Folder 23)
    - Angels Burning, Miscellaneous, 1987 (Box 44, Folder 24)
    - Angels Burning, Printouts, 1987 (Box 44, Folder 25)
    - Angels Burning, Proofs, 1987 (Box 44, Folder 26)
    - California Classics, Correspondence, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - California Classics, Photos, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - California Classics, Preface proofs, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - California Classics, Proofs, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - El Mao, Book Design Materials, 1984 (Box 37, Folder 16)
    - El Mao, Correspondence, 1984 (Box 37, Folder 17)
    - El Mao, MS, 1984 (Box 37, Folder 18-19)
    - El Mao, Proofs, 1984 (Box 37, Folder 20-21)
    - Ocian in View, Printouts, 1987 (Box 44, Folder 27)
    - Ocian in View, Proofs, 1987 (Box 44, Folder 28)
    - Portrait of my Father, correspondence and photos, 1986 (Box 42, Folder 18)
    - Portrait of my Father, MS, 1986 (Box 42, Folder 19)
    - Portrait of my Father, proofs, 1986 (Box 42, Folder 20-23)
    - The Blue Train, Artwork, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - The Blue Train, Galley proof, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - The Blue Train, MS, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - The Blue Train, Paste-ups and page proof, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - The Evening Redness, Page proofs, 1991 (Box 50, Folder 20-22)
    - The Evening Redness, Proofs with edits, 1991 (Box 51, Folder 1-3)
    - The River Between, Corrected page proofs, 1979 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - The River Between, First MS, 1979 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - The River Between, Misc., 1979 (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - The River Between, MS marked for typescript, 1979 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - The River Between, Page proofs, 1979 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - The River Between, Revised MS, 1979 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - The River Between, Third MS, 1979 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Prelutsky, Burt
    - Civilization and Welcome to It, Correspondence, 1987 (Box 44, Folder 29)
  - Rabe, Claire
    - Sicily Enough, Cover design, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Sicily Enough, Misc., 1976 (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Sicily Enough, Proofs, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Reich, Kenneth
    - Making it Happen, correspondence, 1986 (Box 42, Folder 24)
  - Reyes, Carlos
    - The Prisoner, MS and artwork, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - The Prisoner, Proofs, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Ribeiro, Hubert
    - El Peregrino, MS, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Richardson, William
    - The Wound, Art, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - The Wound, MS, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Roditi, Edouard
    - The Disorderly Poet, Art, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - The Disorderly Poet, Proofs, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Ross, Lillian
    - Blaze Allan, correspondence and cover illustrations, 1986 (Box 42, Folder 25)
  - Russell, Ray
    - Holy Horatio, MS, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Holy Horatio, Proofs, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Sanchez, Thomas
    - Starman and the Two Sisters, Proofs, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - The Golden Shovel, Page proof, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - The Man Who Stole the Presidents, MS and artwork, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Sanford, John
    - Adirondack Stories, Corrections and artwork, 1976 (Box 59, Folder Unknown)
    - Adirondack Stories, Galleys, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - Adirondack Stories, MS, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - View from this Wilderness, Artwork and miscellany, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - View from this Wilderness, Galleys, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - View from this Wilderness, Introduction, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - View from this Wilderness, Miscellaneous, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 8)